♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 4=
Mr. Rong, you tried to frame me today.
What an act.
I thought you're only an actor,
but it turns out you're a schemer.
Young Marshal, you flatter me.
I am naturally no match for you.
Otherwise, you would
have been a prisoner by now.
How dare you play tricks here?
Be careful, you might get burned.
Don't worry.
An actor's tricks
are confined to the small stage.
Just you? Think you can
use the Xiaosheng Society to kill me?
Do you believe I'll kill you?
If you truly wanted to kill me,
you wouldn't have only cut my clothes.
Do you really think
the Buddha Head's whereabouts
can save your life?
What if it can't?
How do you know
whether I want to live or die?
After all, the play has just begun.
If I scar this face,
how will you continue the play?
It's just a show.
What are you afraid of, Young Marshal?
You also performed well today.
It was clearly a dead end,
yet you managed to live.
But I will never
let you finish this play alive.
As expected, actors have no loyalty.
I spared your life over and over again,
but you keep pushing your luck.
Loyalty?
You killed my master.
You Governor Mansion
massacred the Rongqing Troupe.
If I could, I would have
killed everyone here already.
I have never met your master.
What makes you so sure
that I killed him?
I saw it. It was with that saber.
You framed me for killing Master.
I will never forgive you
and fight you to the end.
If you truly saw it, you should know
that I did not kill Head Rong.
You've got the wrong target.
Even now, you're still denying it.
By now, you should also understand
that on your own, you can't do
any harm to the Governor.
If you truly want to avenge your master,
then help me find the Buddha Head.
Think I would believe you
with just a few words from you?
Dream on.
Believe it or not,
only I can save you,
and only I can help you.
(Chang'an)
(Mother, don't worry.)
(Shitou is fine.)
When the Rongqing Troupe was arrested,
(Yue Niang, Cleaner of Rongqing Troupe)
she happened to be out buying supplies,
so she escaped.
After learning of the troupe's incident,
she has been hiding.
After extensive investigation,
I finally caught her.
I really didn't do anything.
Please spare my life!
She truly knows nothing
about the Buddha Head.
But Young Marshal seems
to have inextricable ties
to the theft of the Buddha Head.
You seem to prefer to visit
the Governor Mansion late at night.
Sorry to disturb you.
The wedding is approaching,
yet the wedding attire hasn't been made.
So I thought to take one of your suits
to measure your size.
Since you're here, why waste time?
Miss Jiang, please help me
measure my size.
It's better
to leave this to your tailor.
Earlier, you begged me
to spare Rong Xiaonan's life.
Now, you're unwilling
to help me with this small favor?
But don't forget,
his life is still in my hands.
Where is the measuring tape?
Use your hands.
Touching my skin makes you so nervous?
Miss Jiang, do you like me or fear me?
We are not yet married.
So we should keep our distance.
Since you know that...
Why are you still entangled
with that Rong Xiaonan?
Are you treating the Governor Mansion
as a theater troupe?
You're probably overthinking.
Our Jiang family has strict rules.
I have never had such improper behavior
with Mr. Rong as I have with you now.
Touching me is improper?
Then let me show you
what improper behavior is.
♪A thousand sails gone♪
Miss Jiang, you risked your life
to help Rong Xiaonan escape.
You are truly brave and courageous.
♪Suddenly it's dusk♪
Do you really think
that you can hide anything
from me in my house?
♪The moon as before♪
Since you know everything,
then punish me as you please.
Miss Jiang, you are truly heartless.
Do you want me to kill my wife
before the wedding and have my name ruined?
♪Trapped in dawn and dusk♪
♪Candle by the west window♪
♪Burned out this life♪
Miss Jiang, please tell
the measurements to tailors.
Don't delay our wedding.
♪A handful of earth♪
♪The world's last gamble♪
♪Sighing at the late hour♪
♪No one comes to meet me♪
Foster Father,
why call me so early in the morning?
Bring her up.
Rise and speak.
Take a good look. Is it him?
Young Marshal Xu is different
from other guests.
Even when the play started,
he went straight backstage.
He'd talk with Head Rong privately
in the room, shutting everyone out.
That's why I remember.
Do you think you can slander me
with such false accusations?
Besides, with your status,
how could you recognize me?
I...
I recognize your face.
Xu the Demon, the Young Marshal.
Everyone in Fengcheng knows you.
Evidence.
Yes.
I have evidence.
Governor,
it is indeed his army emblem.
That day, I went backstage
to get something
and saw you talking
with Head Rong in the room.
The door was ajar.
I overheard you talking
about the Buddha Head.
I didn't dare linger.
But later, when I went to clean,
I found this under the table.
It was the day he first came
to the Rongqing Troupe.
Governor,
not long after Young Marshal
went to the Rongqing Troupe,
the Buddha Head murder case occurred.
According to Yue Niang's testimony,
on the 16th of last month,
when the Buddha Head was stolen,
Young Marshal also appeared
at the Rongqing Troupe.
Foster Father,
would you believe such absurd testimony?
My engagement to Miss Jiang
was arranged by you.
I've never been to the Rongqing Troupe
to secretly meet Head Rong.
You traitor!
Still denying it?
(Foster Father.)
(So it was you
who wanted to get rid of me.)
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪